Ho Seong, Ahn

20, Seolleung-ro 69-gil, Gangnam-gu, Seoul, Republic of Korea 06217

+82 +10 9655-0787 ahnshy@naver.com



Summary

Software developer, architect, and project manager representative with over 20 years in Korea's leading software developer.

Experienced in developing various business fields, program languages, and platforms.

I also excel in listening carefully to customer requirements, analytical design and implementation software solutions and services that provide value to the customer.

Skills

- Project Manager
- Software Architect
- Software Developer
 - C / C++ / C# / Java / Python
 - Win32 / MFC / WPF
 - Servlet / STS / Spring Boot
 - JavaScript Reat.js
 - JavaScript Vue.js
- Software Engineer
 - svn / git / Jenkins / WAS
- Software Customer Support
- Service Deployment and Operations, Maintenance

Work history

Osstem Implant., Leader of Software dev. team - Incumbenting

- Medical Software FDA and CE Certification Documents Produced
- Orthodontic software V-Ceph, maintenance and new features.
- Development of Practice Management System OneClick v1.1

Co-founder and Leader of Software dev. team – 03/2017 to 07/2020 **ASHINI Co. Ltd.,** Seoul South Korea

- Development of information(documents, images) leakage prevention software solution.
- Development of industrial control security solution.
- Development of server access control security solution.
- Experience with GS(Good Software) certification (ISO/IEC 9126)

Software Developer and Leader of endpoint security dev. team – 03/2014 to 07/2017

SGA Corp, Seoul South Korea

- Development of new version anti virus vaccine software.
- Development of client vulnerability checking and resolving software.
- Experience in obtained C.C.(Common Criteria) cert. (ISO 15408)

Software Developer and Leader of big data governors mgmt. dev. – 07/2013 to 02/2014

Data Streams Corp, Pangyo, Gyeonggi-do, South Korea

• Big Data Governance Management Tools Software Maintenance and New Features Development

Software Developer and Leader of dev. team – 07/2013 to 02/2013 **HANCOM INC,** Pangyo, Gyeonggi-do, South Korea

- Development of new version anti virus vaccine software.
- Development of client vulnerability checking and resolving software.
- Experience with GS(Good Software) certification (ISO/IEC 9126)
- Experience in obtained C.C.(Common Criteria) cert. (ISO 15408)

Development of dental orthodontic software – 12/2011 to 01/2013 **Osstem Implant Co. Ltd.,** Seoul, South Korea

- Maintenance, development of new features.
- Mobile app outsourcing management and source migration for V-Ceph for iPad App.
- Processing dicom images from CT device.

<u>Carrier</u>



Software Developer / Development of editor – 06/2006 to 12/2011 **Namo Interactive Inc.**, Seoul, South Korea

- Development of e-Pub 2.0 WYSIWYG based e-book editing software
- Maintenance, development of WYSIWYG web editor component software development.
- 2D image WYSIWYG editor software development
- Development of http-based software deployment software
- Experience in Samsung SDS, Samsung Electronic, LG Chem.
 Asiana Air Line Software Integrated.

Staff of Enterprise Knowledge Portal dev. team – 08/2006 to 01/2005 **Webplus Co. Ltd.,** Seoul, South Korea

- Web based group software integration.
- Development, construction and maintenance of corporate messengers.
- Development of ActiveX Component.
- Experience in Hyundai Heavy Industries, Hyundai Construction
 & Engineering Group, Hyundai Mipo Dockyard, Hyundai
 Securities, Kolon, NCSoft Software Integrated.

Education

Bachelor of Computer science: University in Korea - 2005

Certificated

- Engineer Information Processing Human Resources
 Development Service of Korea, 2004
- MCP 70-029, SQL Administrator Microsoft in Korea, 2005
- Java Web Programming bitacademy, 2010
 Android Programming Korean Society for Industry & Academy Collaboration, 2011
- iPhone Development Samsung SDS Multicampus, 2012
- ISO 62304/13485 for FDA, CE Certificated DNV in Korea, 2024